Tufts University School of Medicine Yearbook UP150
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine Yearbook, 1924 -- 2020; UP150.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 80 Volumes; 5757 Digital Object(s)
  - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine [yearbook], UP150.001.022.00001 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 58, UP150.001.022.00001.00061 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 59, UP150.001.022.00001.00062 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 60, UP150.001.022.00001.00063 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 61, UP150.001.022.00001.00064 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 62, UP150.001.022.00001.00065 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 63, UP150.001.022.00001.00066 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 64, UP150.001.022.00001.00067 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 65, UP150.001.022.00001.00068 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 66, UP150.001.022.00001.00069 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 67, UP150.001.022.00001.00070 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 68, UP150.001.022.00001.00071 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 69, UP150.001.022.00001.00072 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 70, UP150.001.022.00001.00073 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 71, UP150.001.022.00001.00074 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 72, UP150.001.022.00001.00075 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 73, UP150.001.022.00001.00076 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 74, UP150.001.022.00001.00077 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 75, UP150.001.022.00001.00078 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 76, UP150.001.022.00001.00079 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 77, UP150.001.022.00001.00080 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 78, UP150.001.022.00001.00081 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 79, UP150.001.022.00001.00082 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 80, UP150.001.022.00001.00083 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 81, UP150.001.022.00001.00084 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 82, UP150.001.022.00001.00085 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 83, UP150.001.022.00001.00086 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 84, UP150.001.022.00001.00087 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, page 85, UP150.001.022.00001.00088 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, inside back cover, left, UP150.001.022.00001.00089 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, inside back cover, right, UP150.001.022.00001.00090 (Volume 22)
    - 1962 Tufts University School of Medicine, back cover, UP150.001.022.00001.00091 (Volume 22)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963 [yearbook], UP150.001.023.00001 (Volume 23)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1963.
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, front cover, UP150.001.023.00001.00001 (Volume 23)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1963
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, inside cover (1), UP150.001.023.00001.00002 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, inside cover (2), UP150.001.023.00001.00003 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 1, UP150.001.023.00001.00004 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 2, UP150.001.023.00001.00005 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 3, UP150.001.023.00001.00006 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 4, UP150.001.023.00001.00007 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 5, UP150.001.023.00001.00008 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 6, UP150.001.023.00001.00009 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 7, UP150.001.023.00001.00010 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 8, UP150.001.023.00001.00011 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 9, UP150.001.023.00001.00012 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 10, UP150.001.023.00001.00013 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 11, UP150.001.023.00001.00014 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 12, UP150.001.023.00001.00015 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 13, UP150.001.023.00001.00016 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 14, UP150.001.023.00001.00017 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 15, UP150.001.023.00001.00018 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 16, UP150.001.023.00001.00019 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 17, UP150.001.023.00001.00020 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 18, UP150.001.023.00001.00021 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 19, UP150.001.023.00001.00022 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 20, UP150.001.023.00001.00023 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 21, UP150.001.023.00001.00024 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 22, UP150.001.023.00001.00025 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 23, UP150.001.023.00001.00026 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 24, UP150.001.023.00001.00027 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 25, UP150.001.023.00001.00028 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 26, UP150.001.023.00001.00029 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 27, UP150.001.023.00001.00030 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 28, UP150.001.023.00001.00031 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 29, UP150.001.023.00001.00032 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 30, UP150.001.023.00001.00033 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 31, UP150.001.023.00001.00034 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 32, UP150.001.023.00001.00035 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 33, UP150.001.023.00001.00036 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 34, UP150.001.023.00001.00037 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 35, UP150.001.023.00001.00038 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 36, UP150.001.023.00001.00039 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 37, UP150.001.023.00001.00040 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 38, UP150.001.023.00001.00041 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 39, UP150.001.023.00001.00042 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 40, UP150.001.023.00001.00043 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 41, UP150.001.023.00001.00044 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 42, UP150.001.023.00001.00045 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 43, UP150.001.023.00001.00046 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 44, UP150.001.023.00001.00047 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 45, UP150.001.023.00001.00048 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 46, UP150.001.023.00001.00049 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 47, UP150.001.023.00001.00050 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 48, UP150.001.023.00001.00051 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 49, UP150.001.023.00001.00052 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 50, UP150.001.023.00001.00053 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 51, UP150.001.023.00001.00054 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 52, UP150.001.023.00001.00055 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 53, UP150.001.023.00001.00056 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 54, UP150.001.023.00001.00057 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 55, UP150.001.023.00001.00058 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 56, UP150.001.023.00001.00059 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 57, UP150.001.023.00001.00060 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 58, UP150.001.023.00001.00061 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 59, UP150.001.023.00001.00062 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 60, UP150.001.023.00001.00063 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 61, UP150.001.023.00001.00064 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 62, UP150.001.023.00001.00065 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 63, UP150.001.023.00001.00066 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 64, UP150.001.023.00001.00067 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 65, UP150.001.023.00001.00068 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 66, UP150.001.023.00001.00069 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 67, UP150.001.023.00001.00070 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 68, UP150.001.023.00001.00071 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 69, UP150.001.023.00001.00072 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 70, UP150.001.023.00001.00073 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 71, UP150.001.023.00001.00074 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 72, UP150.001.023.00001.00075 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 73, UP150.001.023.00001.00076 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 74, UP150.001.023.00001.00077 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 75, UP150.001.023.00001.00078 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 76, UP150.001.023.00001.00079 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 77, UP150.001.023.00001.00080 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 78, UP150.001.023.00001.00081 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 79, UP150.001.023.00001.00082 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 80, UP150.001.023.00001.00083 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 81, UP150.001.023.00001.00084 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 82, UP150.001.023.00001.00085 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 83, UP150.001.023.00001.00086 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 84, UP150.001.023.00001.00087 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 85, UP150.001.023.00001.00088 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 86, UP150.001.023.00001.00089 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 87, UP150.001.023.00001.00090 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, page 88, UP150.001.023.00001.00091 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, inside back cover, UP150.001.023.00001.00092 (Volume 23)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1963, back cover, UP150.001.023.00001.00093 (Volume 23)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964 [yearbook], UP150.001.024.00001 (Volume 24)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1964.
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, cover, UP150.001.024.00001.00001 (Volume 24)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1964
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 1, UP150.001.024.00001.00002 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 2, UP150.001.024.00001.00003 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 3, UP150.001.024.00001.00004 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 4, UP150.001.024.00001.00005 (Volume 24)
    - School of Medicine yearbook, 1964, page 5, UP150.001.024.00001.00006 (Volume 24)
      From School of Medicine yearbook, 1964
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 6, UP150.001.024.00001.00007 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 7, UP150.001.024.00001.00008 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 8, UP150.001.024.00001.00009 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 9, UP150.001.024.00001.00010 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 10, UP150.001.024.00001.00011 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 11, UP150.001.024.00001.00012 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 12, UP150.001.024.00001.00013 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 13, UP150.001.024.00001.00014 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 14, UP150.001.024.00001.00015 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 15, UP150.001.024.00001.00016 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 16, UP150.001.024.00001.00017 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 17, UP150.001.024.00001.00018 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 18, UP150.001.024.00001.00019 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 19, UP150.001.024.00001.00020 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 20, UP150.001.024.00001.00021 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 21, UP150.001.024.00001.00022 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 22, UP150.001.024.00001.00023 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 23, UP150.001.024.00001.00024 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 24, UP150.001.024.00001.00025 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 25, UP150.001.024.00001.00026 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 26, UP150.001.024.00001.00027 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 27, UP150.001.024.00001.00028 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 28, UP150.001.024.00001.00029 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 29, UP150.001.024.00001.00030 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 30, UP150.001.024.00001.00031 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 31, UP150.001.024.00001.00032 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 32, UP150.001.024.00001.00033 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 33, UP150.001.024.00001.00034 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 34, UP150.001.024.00001.00035 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 35, UP150.001.024.00001.00036 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 36, UP150.001.024.00001.00037 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 37, UP150.001.024.00001.00038 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 38, UP150.001.024.00001.00039 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 39, UP150.001.024.00001.00040 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 40, UP150.001.024.00001.00041 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 41, UP150.001.024.00001.00042 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 42, UP150.001.024.00001.00043 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 43, UP150.001.024.00001.00044 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 44, UP150.001.024.00001.00045 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 45, UP150.001.024.00001.00046 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 46, UP150.001.024.00001.00047 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 47, UP150.001.024.00001.00048 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 48, UP150.001.024.00001.00049 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 49, UP150.001.024.00001.00050 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 50, UP150.001.024.00001.00051 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 51, UP150.001.024.00001.00052 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 52, UP150.001.024.00001.00053 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 53, UP150.001.024.00001.00054 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 54, UP150.001.024.00001.00055 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 55, UP150.001.024.00001.00056 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 56, UP150.001.024.00001.00057 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 57, UP150.001.024.00001.00058 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 58, UP150.001.024.00001.00059 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 59, UP150.001.024.00001.00060 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 60, UP150.001.024.00001.00061 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 61, UP150.001.024.00001.00062 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 62, UP150.001.024.00001.00063 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 63, UP150.001.024.00001.00064 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 64, UP150.001.024.00001.00065 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 65, UP150.001.024.00001.00066 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 66, UP150.001.024.00001.00067 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 67, UP150.001.024.00001.00068 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 68, UP150.001.024.00001.00069 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 69, UP150.001.024.00001.00070 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 70, UP150.001.024.00001.00071 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 71, UP150.001.024.00001.00072 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 72, UP150.001.024.00001.00073 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 73, UP150.001.024.00001.00074 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 74, UP150.001.024.00001.00075 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 75, UP150.001.024.00001.00076 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 76, UP150.001.024.00001.00077 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 77, UP150.001.024.00001.00078 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 78, UP150.001.024.00001.00079 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 79, UP150.001.024.00001.00080 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 80, UP150.001.024.00001.00081 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 81, UP150.001.024.00001.00082 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 82, UP150.001.024.00001.00083 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 83, UP150.001.024.00001.00084 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 84, UP150.001.024.00001.00085 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 85, UP150.001.024.00001.00086 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 86, UP150.001.024.00001.00087 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 87, UP150.001.024.00001.00088 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, page 88, UP150.001.024.00001.00089 (Volume 24)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1964, back cover, UP150.001.024.00001.00090 (Volume 24)
  - Tufts University 1965 [yearbook], UP150.001.025.00001 (Volume 25)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1965.
    - Tufts University 1965, front cover, UP150.001.025.00001.00001 (Volume 25)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1965
    - Tufts University 1965, page 1, UP150.001.025.00001.00002 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 2, UP150.001.025.00001.00003 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 3, UP150.001.025.00001.00004 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 4, UP150.001.025.00001.00005 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 5, UP150.001.025.00001.00006 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 6, UP150.001.025.00001.00007 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 7, UP150.001.025.00001.00008 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 8, UP150.001.025.00001.00009 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 9, UP150.001.025.00001.00010 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 10, UP150.001.025.00001.00011 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 11, UP150.001.025.00001.00012 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 12, UP150.001.025.00001.00013 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 13, UP150.001.025.00001.00014 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 14, UP150.001.025.00001.00015 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 15, UP150.001.025.00001.00016 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 16, UP150.001.025.00001.00017 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 17, UP150.001.025.00001.00018 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 18, UP150.001.025.00001.00019 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 19, UP150.001.025.00001.00020 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 20, UP150.001.025.00001.00021 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 21, UP150.001.025.00001.00022 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 22, UP150.001.025.00001.00023 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 23, UP150.001.025.00001.00024 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 24, UP150.001.025.00001.00025 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 25, UP150.001.025.00001.00026 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 26, UP150.001.025.00001.00027 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 27, UP150.001.025.00001.00028 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 28, UP150.001.025.00001.00029 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 29, UP150.001.025.00001.00030 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 30, UP150.001.025.00001.00031 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 31, UP150.001.025.00001.00032 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 32, UP150.001.025.00001.00033 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 33, UP150.001.025.00001.00034 (Volume 25)
    - Tufts University 1965, page 34, UP150.001.025.00001.00035 (Volume 25)